

☑ noelcedrix@yahoo.com

3 0995-295-6110

A Obando, Bulacan

www.linkedin.com/in/noelcedrixjoaquin

TECHNICAL SKILLS



SOFT SKILLS

- Excellent verbal and written communication
- Research and Problem-Solving
- Diligent in performing tasks and learning new technologies

INTERESTS

- Anime
- Tekken
- **Figure Collecting**
- Toy Photography

Noel Cedrix Joaquin

Application Support Engineer

Application Support Engineer with over 2 years of experience in areas such as L1 Support and UI Development. Team player with exposure in working with local and international colleagues. Highly motivated in learning new tools and technologies.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Application Support Engineer (L1)

Accenture Inc. - Cigna Bruin

06/2021 - Present

- Technologies utilized: Domino Data Lab, ServiceNow, Python, SQL, Confluence, GitHub, AWS, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Intercom and Dynatrace
- Primary contact of support to over 1700 data scientists and engineers in helping solve problems related to Domino Data Lab, data access, and code in the cloud.
- Create and maintain existing Confluence pages for tracking Jira user stories and documenting common platform issues that also acts as L1 Support runbook.
- Collaborate with engineering team in setting up Dynatrace synthetic alerts to proactively monitor outages within Domino Data Lab.
- Participate in designing and integrating custom bot within Domino Data Lab using Intercom to assist users in resolving common types of issues without the need of submitting a ticket.
- Demonstrate new and common recurring issues, workarounds, and best practices within Domino Data Lab to stakeholders during bi-weekly open forums.
- Lead Python developer for ticket dashboard proof-of-concept for metrics reporting to be consumed by managers and stakeholders.
- Exposure to AWS Cloud technologies such as Redshift, S3, Glue and EC2.
- Created learning materials and trained 2 newly onboarded resources within L1 Support Team.

UI Developer

Accenture Inc. – Cigna Innovation Prod Support

03/2021 - 04/2021

- Technologies utilized: C#, ASP.NET Core MVC, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and MS SQL Server
- Codes according to design specification to produce required functionality.
- Research and implementation of database integration for fetching test data.
- Provide support to senior developers during testing and provision of test data.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Electronics Engineering

Adamson University

06/2013 - 01/2020

TRAININGS

Data and Analytics Bootcamp

Accenture Inc. 01/2021 - 03/2021

Complete Python Bootcamp: From Zero to Hero in Python

Udemy 06/2020